A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, International Division, Office of the Vice President, Office Files of Francis X. Sutton FA568
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Program Files, 1952-1985, bulk 1967-1985; 1967-1985; II
  - Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) -- Reorganization -- Memoranda, Discussion Papers (2 of 2), 1969-1980 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) -- Africa Review Conference (11/7-24/1970) -- Schedule, Participants, Discussion Papers (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) -- Agricultural and Resources Seminar, Khartoum, Sudan, 1980 January 6-9 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) -- East Africa -- Advisory Institute Proposal, Log Notes, Correspondence and Memoranda Re: Visit (1 of 5), 1967 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) -- East Africa -- Correspondence, Memoranda, Notes, Itinerary (2 of 5), 1967 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) -- East Africa -- Correspondence Re: Ethiopia (3 of 5), 1968 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) -- East Africa -- Correspondence and Memoranda Re: Tanzania, Nigeria (4 of 5), 1968-1970 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) -- East Africa -- Nairobi Survey Report (5 of 5), 1972-1978 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) -- East Africa -- Tanzania -- Memoranda, Correspondence, Background Re: Nationalizations, etc., 1967-1976 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) -- East Africa -- Tanzania -- Report, "A Study of the Utilisation of Tanzanian Science Graduates of the University of East Africa, 1962-1966" by James A. Johnson, 1967 August (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) -- East Africa -- Woodman, Everett M. -- Temporary British East Africa Education Consultancy -- Correspondence, Report, 1960 March 31-May 18 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) -- Meeting on Social Science Research on Population (Sep 1971) -- Agenda, Background Papers (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) -- Memoranda Re: Meeting with AID, September Conference of Economic Program Advisors Meeting Materials, Notes, etc. (1 of 3), 1967-1971 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) -- Memoranda, Discussion Papers Re: Economics in Africa, Planning Budget (2 of 3), 1972-1974 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) -- Memoranda Re: Iran, UN Anti-Zionism; Budget Report (3 of 3), 1974-1980 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) -- Mid-East Economic Study (1 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) -- Mid-East Economic Study (2 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) -- North Africa -- Memoranda, Discussion Papers, 1964-1968 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) -- Refugees -- Memoranda, Notes Re: Palestinian Refugees and Senator Javits, 1967-1969 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) -- Report, "Africa Ten Years Later" by Francis X. Sutton, 1970 December (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) -- Southern Africa -- Memoranda, Notes Re: Southern Africa (1 of 2), 1967-1972 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) -- Southern Africa -- Paper on Program Directions, Memoranda (2 of 2), 1972-1978 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) -- Sub-Saharan Africa -- Memoranda Re: Report to Ford Foundation Trustees, 1970 March (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) -- Sudan -- Notes Re: University of Khartoum, Grants, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) -- Turkey -- Memoranda, Grants, Reports, Notes (1 of 3), 1966-1970 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) -- Turkey -- Memoranda, Grants, Reports, Notes (2 of 3), 1974-1976 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) -- Turkey -- Memoranda, Grants, Reports, Notes (3 of 3), 1976-1985 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) -- West Africa -- Ghana --Correspondence from Bob Loken, 1961 March 22-July 5 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) -- West Africa -- Nigeria --Education -- Memoranda, Reports Re: Possible Grants to Universities and Libraries, 1960-1961 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) -- West Africa -- Nigeria -- National Library Services Report, 1961 May 21 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) -- West Africa -- Report, Memoranda, 1967-1972 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Population -- Bellagio Conference (6/13-16/1971)-- Notes, Papers, 1967-1971 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Population -- Bellagio Conference (6/13-16/1971)-- Memoranda, Reports, Background Materials Re: Population Studies and Ford Foundation Work, 1969-1970 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Population -- Bellagio Conference Follow-Up Discussion on Social Science and Management (6/29/1971) -- Memoranda, Reports (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Population -- Conference on Social Science Research on Population and Development (10/29-30/1974) -- Memoranda, Reports, Discussion Papers, Participants List, 1971-1974 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Population -- Conference on Social Science Research on Population and Development (10/29-30/1974) -- Background Papers, 1970-1974 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Population -- Conference on Social Science Research on Population and Development (10/29-30/1974) -- Participants' Memoranda (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Population -- Conference on Social Science Research on Population and Development Follow-Up (1/9-10/1975) -- Agendas, Reports Re: Population, Family Planning, Fertility Studies, 1974-1975 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Population -- Discussion Papers (1 of 3), 1968-1972 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Population -- Discussion Papers (2 of 3), 1973-1977 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Population -- Discussion Papers (3 of 3), 1983 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Population -- General -- Memoranda, Reports Re: Foundation's Population Work, Country Visits, Meetings, Grants, Staff, 1967-1981 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Population -- International Migration Involving Developing Countries -- Research Competition Proposals, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Population -- Lecture, "Progress Possibilities - What Kind? What Direction?" by Oscar Harkavy, 1967 March 15 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Population -- Memoranda Re: International Institute for the Study of Human Reproduction, 1967 August-September (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Population -- Memoranda, Reports Re: Oral Contraceptive Research and Contraceptive Development, 1968 January-December (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Population -- Memoranda, Reports Re: Research Involving Human Subjects, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Population -- Memoranda, Reports Re: Bangladesh Institute and International Center for Health Research, 1977 January-May (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Population -- Memoranda Re: Contraception, Family Planning and Pro-Natalism Issues, 1975-1981 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Population -- Miscellaneous Notes, 1970 June 23 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Population -- Notes, Clippings, Memoranda Re: Budget (1 of 2), 1967-1984 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Population -- Notes, Clippings, Memoranda Re: Budget (2 of 2), 1967-1984 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Population -- Program Evaluations -- Memoranda Re: 6/21/1979 Meeting, 1979 June (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Population -- Reports Re: Pakistan and India, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Population -- Report, "Population Information Paper" by Oscar Harkavy, 1979 August (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Population -- Reproductive Planning -- Notes, Memoranda, Paper, Budget, 1966-1985 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Population Council -- Budget Information, Organizational Chart, Notes for 6/22-23/1972 Meeting, 1971-1972 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Population Council -- Evaluations of Council Work and 9/25/1979 Meeting Materials, 1979 September (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Population Council -- Report, "Financing the Population Council" by Frederick O'R. Hayes, 1979 September 21 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Program Management -- Notes, Memoranda (1 of 3), 1974 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Program Management -- Notes, Drafts (2 of 3), 1975 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Program Management -- Notes, Drafts, and Background (3 of 3), 1976-1978 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Public Management -- Governments and Development Draft Paper, 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Public Management -- Report, "A Management Consultancy and Training Strategy for Public Management" by Robert W. Kerwin, circa 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Public Management -- Report, "Observations on Public Management Trends in Africa and the Middle East" by George F. Gant, 1973 January (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Public Management -- Review -- Memoranda, Notes, Background Materials, 1967-1976 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Public Management -- Review Papers for ID Conference (9/1975), 1975 September (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Publications -- Ford Foundation Reports in First Author Order, 1969 January 27 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Refugees and Migration -- General -- Notes, Memoranda, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Refugees and Migration -- Indochina -- Schedule, Notes, Memoranda, etc., 1979 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Refugees and Migration -- Information Paper and Memoranda, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Refugees and Migration -- Memoranda, Notes, Background, 1972-1980 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Rural Development -- Agricultural Development Council (A/D/C) Meeting (2/16/1973) Materials -- Memoranda, Reports Re: Political Economy of Development, 1970-1973 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Science and Technology -- International Science -- Memoranda, Progress Reports, Notes, Grant Recommendations (1 of 2), 1968-1979 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Science and Technology -- International Science -- Memoranda, Progress Reports, Notes, Grant Recommendations (2 of 2), 1968-1979 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Science and Technology -- United Nations Conference -- Memoranda, Draft Papers (1 of 2), 1978-1979 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Science and Technology -- United Nations Conference -- Memoranda, Draft Papers (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Self-Study -- Budget -- Memoranda (1 of 2), 1971-1972 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Self-Study -- Budget -- Memoranda (2 of 2), 1971-1972 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Self-Study -- General -- Memoranda Re: Communication, Grant Requests, Study Process, etc.; Notes, Background Materials (1 of 4), 1971 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Self-Study -- General (2 of 4), 1971 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Self-Study -- General (3 of 4), 1972 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Self-Study -- General (4 of 4), 1972 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Self-Study -- Interviews -- Memoranda and Excerpts (1 of 3), 1971-1972 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Self-Study -- Interviews -- Notes, Interview Excerpts, Memoranda (2 of 3), 1971-1972 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Self-Study -- Interviews -- Notes, Interview Excerpts, Memoranda (3 of 3), 1971-1972 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Trustees Planning Project -- Discussion Papers (1 of 3), 1976 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Trustees Planning Project -- Discussion Papers (2 of 3), 1976 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Trustees Planning Project -- Discussion Papers (3 of 3), 1976 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Trustees Planning Project -- Review -- Notes and Memoranda Re: Discussion Papers (1 of 3), 1975 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Trustees Planning Project -- Review -- Notes and Memoranda Re: Discussion Papers (2 of 3), 1976 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Trustees Planning Project -- Review -- Notes and Memoranda Re: Discussion Papers (3 of 3), 1976 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Urban Affairs -- Conferences, Meetings -- Delos Symposium (7/3-10/1970) -- Memorandum, Report Re: Human Settlement in Developing Countries (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Urban Affairs -- Conferences, Meetings -- Bellagio Conference, "Social Science Research and Development" (2/13-15/1974) -- Memoranda, Report, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Urban Affairs -- Conferences, Meetings -- Social Science Meeting (5/3/1974) -- Memoranda, Notes, Reports, Background/Reference Materials, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Urban Affairs -- Conferences, Meetings -- Social Science Research and Rural Development Meetings, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Urban Affairs -- International Urbanization Survey -- Memoranda, Meeting Materials, Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Urban Affairs -- International Urbanization Survey -- Report, "Urbanization in Morocco" by Katherine Marshall Johnson (separated), undated (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Urban Affairs -- International Urbanization Survey -- Report, "Urbanization in Nigeria" by Leslie Green and Vincent Milone (separated), undated (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Urban Affairs -- International Urbanization Survey -- Report, "Urbanization in Tropical Africa" by Colin Rosser (separated), undated (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Urban Affairs -- International Urbanization Survey -- Report, "Urbanization in Zambia" by Alan J.F. Simmance (separated), undated (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Urban Affairs -- Rural Development, Population Studies, Education, Technological Development, Social Research -- Memoranda, Reports, 1968-1975 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Urban Poverty -- Grant Recommendation Re: Birzeit University Community Outreach Programs, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - USIAP -- Polish Crisis -- Memoranda, Correspondence, Trustees Report, Notes, Background (1 of 4), 1981-1982 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - USIAP -- Polish Crisis -- Memoranda, Notes, Grant Proposals, Background (2 of 4), 1981-1982 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - USIAP -- Polish Crisis -- Consultant Report, Notes, Correspondence, Background Information (3 of 4), 1981-1982 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - USIAP -- Polish Crisis -- Notes and Background (4 of 4), 1981-1982 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Values Conference (3/6/1974) -- Memoranda, Notes, Background Re: American Values, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Trip Files, 1957-1980; III
  Dr. Sutton's trip files document the meetings and conferences he attended and the country visits he made from 1957 through 1980. The files contain itineraries, reports, background information, pre-trip logistics and post-visit observations, as well as agendas, meeting books and materials prepared for and following the Foundation's international conferences. Dr. Sutton's trip files offer firsthand accounts of the developed and developing countries within which the International Division operated and detail the need for continued Foundation support in many of the regions. The files reveal the frequency and pace with which Dr. Sutton and his colleagues in the International Division traveled, often attending multiple conferences each month, and stopping in several countries and occasionally on different continents during a single trip.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - Africa Mission II -- Itinerary, Correspondence, Background Materials (see: Visual Materials), 1957-1958 March (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Paris, Tunisia, Beirut -- Feb 1960 -- Report and Memoranda, 1960 January-April (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Ghana, Nigeria, Tunisia, Ivory Coast -- Itinerary, Memoranda Re: Visit Reports, 1960 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Congo, Dakar, Ghana, Senegal -- Memoranda, Trip Reports, 1961 May (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Oxford Conference on Tensions on Development (8/28-9/1/1961) -- Itinerary, Memoranda Re: Meetings and Proposals; Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - International Division Representatives Meeting -- Beirut -- Notes and Discussion Papers (1 of 2), 1967 January 9-11 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - International Division Representatives Meeting -- Beirut -- Notes and Discussion Papers (2 of 2), 1967 January 9-11 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Argentina, Brazil, Chile, Caribbean -- Itinerary, Notes, Background Materials, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Brazil -- Background Material -- Schedule, Organization, Grants, Appendix (1 of 2), 1967 October 9-21 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Brazil -- Background Material -- Schedule, Organization, Grants, Appendix (2 of 2), 1967 October 9-21 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - International Division Representatives Meeting -- Nairobi -- Memoranda, Discussion Papers, 1968 June 6-8 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Japan -- Itinerary, Notes, Background Material, 1968 October (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Japan -- Report, 1968 October (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Indonesia -- Correspondence, Itinerary, Notes, 1968 October (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - India -- Notes, Memoranda, Background Materials, 1968 October (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Africa -- Correspondence, 1969 June (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - International Division Representatives Meeting -- Mexico City -- Reports, Discussion Papers (1 of 3), 1969 December 3-5 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - International Division Representatives Meeting -- Mexico City -- Reports, Discussion Papers (2 of 3), 1969 December 3-5 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - International Division Representatives Meeting -- Mexico City -- Reports, Discussion Papers (3 of 3), 1969 December 3-5 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Bangkok -- Education -- Schedule, Memoranda, Background Material, 1970 October (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Europe (Germany) -- Correspondence, Memoranda, 1971 October (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Peru -- Schedule, Directory, Briefing Materials, circa 1972 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Middle East, Africa, and Europe -- Visit and Report, 1972 November (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - International Division Conference -- Agenda, Reports, Memoranda, Discussion Papers (1 of 4), 1973 September (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - International Division Conference -- Agenda, Reports, Memoranda, Discussion Papers (2 of 4), 1973 September (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - International Division Conference -- Agenda, Reports, Memoranda, Discussion Papers (3 of 4), 1973 September (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - International Division Conference -- Agenda, Reports, Memoranda, Discussion Papers (4 of 4), 1973 September (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Asia -- Perceptions Report, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Latin America -- Notes, Schedule, 1974 October (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Russia -- Correspondence, Memoranda, 1975 August (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - International Division Conference -- Invitees, Memoranda, Discussion Papers (1 of 3), 1975 September (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - International Division Conference -- Invitees, Memoranda, Discussion Papers (2 of 3), 1975 September (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - International Division Conference -- Invitees, Memoranda, Discussion Papers (3 of 3), 1975 September (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Asia/Europe -- Schedule, Memoranda, 1977 February-March (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Latin America -- Chile, Argentina, Peru -- Reflections Paper, 1977 November (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Africa/India Trip -- Itinerary, Memoranda, Background, 1978 October (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - International Division Conference -- Invitees, Memoranda, Papers, 1979 January (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Sudan -- Itinerary, Agenda, Notes, Background, 1980 January (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - China, Manila, Jakarta, Bangkok -- Correspondence, Memoranda, Background Re: Chinese Law, 1980 May (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Budget Files, 1966-1983; IV
  This series contains budget and expenditure reports, interoffice memoranda, background materials, and notes regarding the finances and accounting practices of the Foundation's International Division. Budget reports and appropriations summaries trace the Foundation's grant funding through several fiscal years, recording active and completed grants as well as actual and proposed program budgets. Subjects addressed within the series include the Foundation's long-range financial plans, budget cuts, program commitments and funding requirements, management costs, and overseas staffing and compensation.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Budget Backup -- Programs -- Quarterly Reports, Memoranda, Budgets, Information Papers (1 of 4), 1973 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Budget Backup -- Programs -- Quarterly Reports, Memoranda, Budgets, Information Papers (2 of 4), 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Budget Backup -- Programs -- Quarterly Reports, Memoranda, Budgets, Information Papers (3 of 4), 1974-1977 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Budget Backup -- Programs -- Quarterly Reports, Memoranda, Budgets, Information Papers (4 of 4), 1977-1978 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Budget Discussion Meeting -- Notes, Projections, Background Memoranda, 1974 September (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Budget -- Fiscal Year 1974-1975 (Pre-cuts) -- Memoranda (1 of 2), 1972 January-1973 February (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Budget -- Fiscal Year 1974-1975 (Pre-cuts) -- Memoranda (2 of 2), 1973 February-1974 March (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Budget -- Fiscal Year 1974-1975 (1 of 4), 1973 May-June (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Budget -- Fiscal Year 1974-1975 (2 of 4), 1973 June-November (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Budget -- Fiscal Year 1974-1975 (3 of 4), 1974 April-July (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Budget -- Fiscal Year 1974-1975 -- Memoranda (4 of 4), 1974 August-1975 January (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Budget -- 1980 -- Memoranda, Discussion Papers Re: Long-Range Budget (1 of 3), 1974 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Budget -- 1980 (2 of 3), 1974 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Budget -- 1980 (3 of 3), 1974 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Budget -- General -- Memoranda Re: Personnel, Planning, Grants; Budgets; Background (1 of 5), 1974 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Budget -- General (2 of 5), 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Budget -- General (3 of 5), 1975 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Budget -- General (4 of 5), 1975-1976 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Budget -- General (5 of 5), 1976-1980 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Dependent Organizations and Forward Commitments -- Memoranda, Information Paper, 1968-1971 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Development Assistance -- Completed Grants and Projects (1951-1968) (1 of 2), circa 1968 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Development Assistance -- Completed Grants and Projects (1951-1968) (2 of 2), circa 1968 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Development Assistance -- Interim Reports No. 38, 39 -- Appropriations Summaries, 1968 March-June (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Development Assistance -- Standard Report No. 41 -- Appropriations Summaries, Status of Active Grants and Projects -- General and Asia (1 of 3), 1968 September 30 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Development Assistance -- Standard Report No. 41 -- Appropriations Summaries, Status of Active Grants and Projects -- MEA (2 of 3), 1968 September 30 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Development Assistance -- Standard Report No. 41 -- Appropriations Summaries, Status of Active Grants and Projects -- LAC, NY and Non-Regular (3 of 3), 1968 September 30 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Management Costs Plan -- Memoranda, Report, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Management Costs -- Retrenchment -- Memoranda, Progress Reports, 1975 February-July (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Management Costs -- Proposed Budget Fiscal Year 1976, 1975 September (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Management Costs -- Proposed Budget Fiscal Year 1977, 1976 September (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Management Costs -- Memoranda Re: Regional Cost Reduction in International Division, 1980-1981 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Office for Latin America and the Caribbean (OLAC) -- Program Plans and Funding Request FY 1978-1979, 1977 February (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Overseas Compensation Study -- Memoranda and Notes (folder 1 of 2), 1967-1969 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Overseas Compensation Study -- Memoranda and Notes (folder 2 of 2), 1969-1974 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Overseas Compensation Study -- Report, 1977 April 29 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Overseas Compensation -- Memoranda, Report (folder 1 of 5), 1980 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Overseas Compensation -- Memoranda (folder 2 of 5), 1980 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Overseas Compensation -- Memoranda Re: Taxes, Personnel Policy Manual, Report (folder 3 of 5), 1980 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Overseas Compensation -- Memoranda Re: Draft Report (folder 4 of 5), 1980 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Overseas Compensation -- Memoranda (folder 5 of 5), 1980 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Overseas Compensation -- Review -- Working Group -- Forms, Memoranda Re: Tax Withholding, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Overseas Compensation -- Taxes -- Memoranda and Discussion Paper (folder 1 of 2), 1977-1980 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Overseas Compensation -- Taxes -- Memoranda and Discussion Paper (folder 2 of 2), 1977-1980 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Overseas Development -- Completed Grants and Projects (1951-1967) (1 of 2), circa 1967 (Box 78, Folder 9)